(Sheldon:)For the record, I should let you know...
(Sheldon:)...this is my first time
driving an actual motor vehicle.
(Penny:)-You have your learner's permit, right?
-Yes.
And I've logged a considerable number
of hours on a simulator.
(Sheldon:)-Good.
-Didn't work out well.
-All right. Can we go?
-One moment.
(Sheldon:)According to my Driver's Ed book,
the side mirror is properly adjusted...
...when a portion of the driver's door
handle is visible in the lower right corner.
There's the handle. Back. Too far.
(Sheldon:)Bringing it back.
Optimized. Ahem.
(Sheldon:)Now, where is the switch
to adjust the passenger-side mirror?
(Penny:)It's right there.
Where is the passenger-side mirror?
(Penny:)In a parking lot in Hollywood.
(Penny:)-Now, can we please go?
-Yes. Soon as I adjust my seat.
(Sheldon:)Whee!